(Penny:)Okay, I'll go to a hotel.
(Penny:)Text me in the morning
if you're still alive.
(Leonard:)Uh, Theodore,
(Leonard:)how long
(Leonard:)are you planning
to stay exactly?
(Theodore:)Oh, thanks to the coins
I found in your couch,
(Theodore:)a day longer than I thought.
(Leonard:)This is ridiculous.
(Theodore:)I like the painting.
(Theodore:)Is that your mom?
Sheldon, get out here!
(Sheldon:)Will you keep it down?
(Sheldon:)What kind of vengeful
bed and breakfast
(Sheldon:)do you think I'm running?
(Leonard:)We lived together
13 years.
(Leonard:)How can you be so awful to me?
I'm being awful?!
(Sheldon:)You're the one who went
out of your way to hurt me.
(Leonard:)Because you were
being selfish.
(Sheldon:)Dividing our belongings
is difficult.
(Leonard:)Why?
I said I didn't care!
(Theodore:)Excuse me.
(Theodore:)It's none of my business,
but it sounds like a lot
(Theodore:)of this anger
is coming from love.